(Raj:)He broke out
and poisoned Gotham's water supply.
(Howard:)Well...
(Sheldon:)...I suppose I could poison Kripke.
(Leonard:)-No, no.
SHELDON: It's a simple matter.
(Sheldon:)There are several toxic chemicals
that would be untraceable in an autopsy.
Okay, that's the spirit...
...but let's dial it back
to a nonlethal form of vengeance.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
How about we put a whoopee cushion
on his office chair?
He'll sit down and it'll sound
like he's flatulent even though he's not.
(Leonard:)Let's keep thinking.
(Penny:)Oh, gee, you're too late.
(Penny:)Scarlett Johansson
and Wonder Woman were here...
(Penny:)...trolling around
for neurotic little weasels.
(Howard:)I came to talk to Bernadette.
She's working today, right?
(Penny:)-I don't think she wants to see you.
-Why not?
Come on. You hurt her feelings
by not calling her all week.